

ANANDHU CHANDRAN I

GRAPHIC DESIGNER

9645960593

anandhuchandran.j@gmail.com

About Me

A Graphic designer with professional experience in field of design, branding and social media.

A team player; experienced in professional multicultural communication.

Goal- oriented, positive thinker, openminded and friendly, respectful towards collective goals, colleagues and deadlines.

My goal is to deliver high quality result which benefits my clients' bussiness and their personal objectives.

Address

Anandha Vilasam, Elavinkuzhi, Vanda, Karippoor PO, Nedumangdu, TVM, Kerala Pin: 695541

Personal Details

Date of Birth: May 30 Marital Status : Single

Nationality

: Indian

Language

: English, Malayalam, Tamil

Hindi

Reference

Vijayan C Panicker

Chairman & CEO (Flexi Financial Solutions)

vijayancpanicker@flexifinsolutions.com 8921999322



linkedin.com/in/anandhu-chandran-i/



behance.net/anandhu_chandran_J



dribbble.com/anandhu_chandran_j



@anandhu_chandran_j

Experience

Nexlark (Graphic Designer and Social Media Handler) Dec 2021 - Ongoing

Here I work as graphic designer and social media handler, and my main tasks include creating infographics and lifestyle design, as well as handling their social media platforms like Facebook.

Flexi Financial Solutions (Creative Designer) Nov 2020 - Dec 2021

Their Corporate Logo and total branding was done by me, and my main task was to update their corporate profile and create their social media promotions.

Mindway Designs (Visual Designer & Video Editor) June 2018 - Jan 2020

Besides editing videos for several clients, I contribute to creating several books under Kerala Chalachitra Academy. I am proud to say that I was part of several books published there as well.

Projects

Movie Title - O - Graphy

Graphic Assistant

- Study of Typography
- with focus on 90 years of Malayalam Movies
- Kerala Chalachitra Academy

IFFK Hand Book

Layout Assistant

- International Filim Festival Kerala (IFFK) 2019
- Dec 06>13 TVM, Kerla
- Kerala Chalachitra Academy
- Department of Cultural Affairs Govt. of Kerala

Branding (FFS)

Creative Designer

- Logo Designed
- Stationery and Branding
- Corporate Profile
- Social Media Posts

Branding

Freelance

- Logo Designed
- Stationery and Branding
- Social Media Posts

Education

LMCST, Kuttichal

2013 - 2017 B-Tech (EEE)

C-DIT (CyberSri)

2017 - 2018

Visual Effects and 3D Animtion

LBS Centre

2018

Diploma in Computer Application (S)

Skills

Digital

- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Indesign
- Adobe Illustrator
- Adobe Flash
- Adobe Premire Pro
- Adobe After Effects
- Autodesk Maya
- Visual Effects
- Microsoft Office
- corelDRAW
- Figma
- DaVinci Resolve